we need to
modify the code that we have been given
so that double quotes are used in our
string
rather than single quotes
and we've been given an example of the
expected output
let's start just by running our code as
it is
and you can see that our code already
matches the expected output
the code that was output looks a little
bit different than the string that we
see on line 1.
when using single quotes around our
string we need to escape any single
quotes within the string
if we didn't our output would not be as
expected
you can see that we have a syntax error
so when using single quotes around our
string we need to escape
single quotes within the string
now this problem asks us to use double
quotes instead
so let's replace the single quotes
around our string
with double quotes
now when we run our code we see the
expected output
however since we're now using double
quotes around our string
we no longer need to escape these single
quotes within the string
running our code again you can see that
we still see that expected output
according to the ruby style guide it's
preferred that we use
double quotes around our string when we
need to have single quotes within it
rather than using single quotes around
the string and
escaping single quotes within the string